[
    {
        'questionNumber':1,
        'question':'I like ...... in my spare time.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'reading',
        'option2':'read',
        'option3':'to read',
        'option4':'to reading',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'reading'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':2,
        'question':'I went to the bookshop ...... "Harry Potter". ',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'For buying',
        'option2':'to buy',
        'option3':'to buying',
        'option4':'for to buy',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'to buy'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':3,
        'question':'He is interested ...... learning Romanian.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'in',
        'option2':'on',
        'option3':'to',
        'option4':'for',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'in'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':4,
        'question':'Would you like ...... to drink, Sir?',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'anything',
        'option2':'anywhere',
        'option3':'nothing',
        'option4':'something',
        'answerNumber':4,
        'answer':'something'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':5,
        'question':'What ...... next weekend?',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'do you do',
        'option2':'are you doing',
        'option3':'will you do',
        'option4':'did you do',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'are you doing'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':6,
        'question':'How many students in your class ...... from Bangladesh?',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'comes',
        'option2':'come',
        'option3':'came',
        'option4':'are coming',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'come'
    }, 
    {
        'questionNumber':7,
        'question':'I am hungry. I want two ...... of chicken.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'plates',
        'option2':'pieces',
        'option3':'bowls',
        'option4':'gasses',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'pieces'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':8,
        'question':'They are ugly and expensive; ...... people buy them.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'though',
        'option2':'yet',
        'option3':'still',
        'option4':'besides',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'yet'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':9,
        'question':'What time ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'the train leaves?',
        'option2':'leaves the train?',
        'option3':'is the train leaving',
        'option4':'does the train leave',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'the train leaves'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':10,
        'question':'I promise I ...... study harder.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'will',
        'option2':'am going to',
        'option3':'may',
        'option4':'must',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'will'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':11,
        'question':'How long ...... English?',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'are you learning',
        'option2':'have you been learning',
        'option3':'do you learn',
        'option4':'you learn',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'have you been learning'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':12,
        'question':'I hope that a school ...... for village children.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'opens',
        'option2':'is opened',
        'option3':'has to be opened',
        'option4':'be opened',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'opens'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':13,
        'question':'Closest similar meaning of word "compunction" is ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'remorse',
        'option2':'merciful',
        'option3':'connive',
        'option4':'recklessness',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'remorse'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':14,
        'question':'Closest similar meaning of word "demolish" is ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'repair',
        'option2':'consume',
        'option3':'humiliate',
        'option4':'destroy',
        'answerNumber':4,
        'answer':'destroy'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':15,
        'question':'Closest similar meaning of word "beneficient" is ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'charitable',
        'option2':'imagery',
        'option3':'profitable',
        'option4':'cost-effective',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'charitable'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':16,
        'question':'Closest similar meaning of word "mendacity" is ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'mandatory',
        'option2':'untruthfulness',
        'option3':'veracity',
        'option4':'potential',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'untruthfulness'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':17,
        'question':'Closest similar meaning of word "theocracy" is ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'hierocracy',
        'option2':'ideology',
        'option3':'conservative',
        'option4':'chruch state',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'ideology'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':18,
        'question':'Closest opposite meaning of word "integrate" is ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'accommodate',
        'option2':'compose',
        'option3':'articulate',
        'option4':'segregate',
        'answerNumber':4,
        'answer':'segregate'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':19,
        'question':'Closest opposite meaning of word "Calm" is ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'excited',
        'option2':'restful',
        'option3':'cool',
        'option4':'serene',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'excited'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':20,
        'question':'Closest opposite meaning of word "wordy" is ......',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'rambling',
        'option2':'concise',
        'option3':'diffuse',
        'option4':'voluble',
        'answerNumber':2,
        'answer':'concise'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':21,
        'question':'A teacher needs to discuss in classes, it ...... curiosity in students.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'creates',
        'option2':'created',
        'option3':'create',
        'option4':'will creates',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'creates'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':22,
        'question':'Successful people always ...... two things: one determination and second, sincerity'.,
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'had',
        'option2':'doing',
        'option3':'did',
        'option4':'have',
        'answerNumber':4,
        'answer':'have'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':23,
        'question':'They like swimming, whenever they have a leisure time.(Which word is a verbal noun?)',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'Leisure',
        'option2':'free',
        'option3':'like',
        'option4':'swimming',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'Leisure'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':24,
        'question':'Nobody likes heap of garbage in front of his house.(Which word is a collective noun?)',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'leap of garbage',
        'option2':'in front',
        'option3':'house',
        'option4':'likes',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'leap of garage'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':25,
        'question':'Find interrogative pronoun in sentence."Why did you not call me? This made me alarmed',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'you',
        'option2':'me',
        'option3':'why',
        'option4':'did',
        'answerNumber':3,
        'answer':'why'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':26,
        'question':'Right grammatical category of the underlined phrase in the sentence,"Ram handed a book to his sister" is ',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'complement',
        'option2':'direct object',
        'option3':'adjunct',
        'option4':'indirect object',
        'answerNumber':4,
        'answer':'indirect object'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':27,
        'question':'Which of the following is noun?',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'real',
        'option2':'readable',
        'option3':'reliable',
        'option4':'reality',
        'answerNumber':4,
        'answer':'reality'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':28,
        'question':'English is today the third ...... native language worldwide after Chinese and Hindi, with some 380 million speakers.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'the most spoken',
        'option2':'the more spoken',
        'option3':'much spoken',
        'option4':'most spoken',
        'answerNumber':3,
        'answer':'much spoken'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':29,
        'question':'We could barely get any information at the airport ...... people seemed to have ...... idea about the flights.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'Many / any',
        'option2':'A lot of / any',
        'option3':'Few / no',
        'option4':'Only a few / some',
        'answerNumber':3,
        'answer':'Few / no'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':30,
        'question':'...... his friends speaks any English.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'Some',
        'option2':'All',
        'option3':'Many',
        'option4':'Neither of',
        'answerNumber':4,
        'answer':'Neither of'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':31,
        'question':'These differences between two photographs ...... with the help of Photoshop',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'should remove',
        'option2':'have to remove',
        'option3':'could have been removed',
        'option4':'must have removed',
        'answerNumber':3,
        'answer':'could have been removed'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':32,
        'question':'New legislation ...... in congress but it ...... by many.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'was introduced / wasn`t accepted ',
        'option2':'was introduced / didn`t accept',
        'option3':'is introduced / won`t accept',
        'option4':'introduced / hadn`t been accepted',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'was introduced / wasn`t accepted'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':33,
        'question':'Mike has been told he will have to pay the fine ...... his high rank in the military.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'even if',
        'option2':'furthermore',
        'option3':'despite',
        'option4':'on purpose that',
        'answerNumber':3,
        'answer':'despite'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':34,
        'question':'The economy in China is booming; ..... many foreign investors are planning to enter China`s market.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'Nonetheless',
        'option2':'so as to',
        'option3':'in addition to',
        'option4':'that`s why ',
        'answerNumber':4,
        'answer':'that`s why'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':35,
        'question':'I wish you ..... making that noise. It`s bothering me.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'would stop',
        'option2':'are going to stop',
        'option3':'stop',
        'option4':'can stop',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'would stop'
    },
    {
        'questionNumber':36,
        'question':'..... more help, I could call my neighbour.',
        'category':'English',
        'option1':'Needed',
        'option2':'are go  ing to stop',
        'option3':'stop',
        'option4':'can stop',
        'answerNumber':1,
        'answer':'would stop'
    },


  
]